freshome.com 2019-06-24

# Privacy Policy | Freshome.com

### Privacy Policy

Freshome, respects your privacy and is committed to protecting personal information you may provide us through our website.

This privacy policy explains what information may be collected on our website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties.

We urge you to read this privacy policy so that you understand our commitment to you and your privacy, and how you can contribute to that commitment.

### The Information We Collect and How We Use It

Our Website typically collects two types of information about you:

Information that you provide that personally identifies you

When you create an account, we collect your name, email address and password. You may also choose to provide additional information such as your location, personal photo and photos you add to your collections. We use the information to improve our service to you, provide you with updates, or to respond to your requests.

Whether or not you provide this information is your choice; however, in many instances this type of information is required to participate in the particular activity, realize a benefit we may offer, or gain access to certain content on our website.

Information that does not personally identify you, that we automatically collect when you visit our Website

If you do not create an account, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. We typically collect and store details about your visit such as your IP address, browser type, browser language, the pages you visit, the date and time you access our website, if you linked to our website from another website, and the address of that website. Gathering your information helps us ensure our website and other services work correctly and support our customer analytic efforts.

By visiting our website or using any of our services, you consent to our collection, use, disclosure, transfer and storage of information relating to you as set forth in this policy.

#### Use of Cookies

We may collect information about your use of our website through cookies and similar technology. A “cookie” is a small file we transfer to your computer, so we can keep track of your interests and/or preferences and recognize you as a return visitor. For example, we may use these technologies to collect information about ways visitors use our websites, to support the features and functionality of our websites, and to personalize your experience when you use our website. 

This website also uses a tool called Google Analytics to collect information about your use of this site. The tool uses cookies to collect standard internet log and visitor behavior information. This information is used to optimize the functionality of our site and serve ads to you based on your past visits. You may opt-out of Google Analytics cookies by visiting this link.

If you don’t want us to use cookies when you use our website, you will need to change your internet browser settings so that your browser does not accept them. For more information about cookies, visit the help page for your web browser or see http:www.allaboutcookies.org. Please note that if you disable your web browser’s cookies and other technologies, certain features of our website and services will be disabled and you will limit the functionality we can provide when you visit our site.

#### Affiliate Marketing Programs and Third-Party Cookies

We are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites. Freshome may also participate in other third-party affiliate marketing programs that allow Freshome to earn commissions when you click on (and/or make purchases using) links to companies, brands, products, and/or services on the Freshome site. To help keep track of the commissions we earn, the companies who provide these programs may place third-party cookies on your computer or mobile device. By clicking on links on Freshome, you consent to placement and use of cookies as described in the privacy policies on those provider’s sites.

#### Links to Other Sites

Freshome has links to partners and other sites. When you link to another site, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new website.

#### Data Retention

We will retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this privacy policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. 

#### California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits users of our website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make a request, please contact us using the email or mailing address at the end of this policy. 

#### Collection of Information from Children

We recognize the importance of protecting the privacy and safety of children, our website and services are directed towards a general audience and are not directed towards children. We do not knowingly collect information about children under the age of 13 or minors otherwise defined in local law or regulation without verifiable parental consent. If we learn that someone under 13 has provided personal information through one of our websites, we will use reasonable efforts to remove that information from our databases. 

#### Restriction of Liability

Freshome.com makes no claims, promises or guarantees about the accuracy, completeness, or adequacy of the contents of this website and expressly disclaims liability for errors and omissions in the contents of this website.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may review and update this privacy policy periodically without any prior notice. We will post a notice to our website to inform you of any material changes to our privacy policy and indicate when it was most recently updated. 

#### Contact Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

Freshome  
1423 Red Ventures Drive  
Fort Mill, SC 29707  
United States  
Email: admin@freshome.com

Last Updated: 3/18/2019
